

Do Anh Tu

Java developer

Date of birth: Jan 08, 1995

Gender: Male

Phone: 0397872462

Email: anhtuhd95@gmail.com
Address: Hai Duong, Vietnam
Website: https://tubean.github.io/

PROFILE

I am a Java developer, I have done several projects Java web applications. I have had a lot of experience in teamwork and working in Agile. I am a hard-working, willing to explore new technologies. I look forward to working in a professional and challenging environment. Outside of work, I'm passionate about reading, soccer and play games...

INTERESTS

I like soccer, music, playing game and sharing my knowledge

EDUCATION

2013 - May 2016	National University of Science and Technology "MISiS" Major: Information Technology One of a few students from Vietnam who received scholarships from the Russian government
2016 - ????	Đại học Trực tuyến FUNiX

CERTIFICATIONS

2017	Certificate 1 in Funix: Digital Passport
2018	Certificate 2 in Funix: Moblile Application Developer
2019	Certificate 3 in Funix: Enterprise Application Developer

SKILLS

Language	English
Framework	 Spring Framework: Spring MVC, Spring Boots Bootstrap 3 Framework MyBatis, Hibernate Struts 2 Seasar JavaEE

- Redis

Program languages	Java, Java Script, HTML and CSS, MYSQL
Development tools	Intellij JetBrain, Eclipse, Notepad++, Navicat, WorkBench, Mobaxterm,
Management tools	Maven, Git, Jira, Bitbucket
Others skills	Agile and Scrum, Training, Making plan, Searching and Improving myself

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mar 2020 - now	Java Developer at VinSmart Develop back-end web application Main responsibilities: Worked as a member of the company's Java team and developed a microservice system based on Spring Boot
Mar 2019 - Feb 2020	Java Developer at BMBSOFT Vietnam Develop back-end web application Main responsibilities: Worked as a member of the company's Java team and developed an application using Spring Boot, JavaEE framework.
Sep 2018 - Feb 2019	Java Developer at Mulodo Vietnam Co., Ltd., Develop a logistics web application Main responsibilities: Worked as a member of the company's Java team and developed an application using Spring Boot, Seasar framework.
Jun 2017 - Sep 2018	Junior Java Developer at Higgsup Co,.Ltd Develop a logistics web application Main responsibilities: - Involved in Analysis, design, and coding in J2EE environment - Fix bug, maintain and migrate web application.
Nov 2016 - May 2016	Fresher in Higgsup Co,.Ltd Fresher Main responsibilities: - Participate in seminars about Java Core, Web application - "Pair Programming", review code with juniors and seniors Write the summary after every event or topics.

PROJECTS

EMS (Elements manage system)

(3/2020 - now)

Customer	VinSmart (Telecommunication Equipment Research Institude)
Description	- An Element Management System (EMS) manages specific types of one or more network elements within a telecommunication management network (TMN)
Team size	13
My position	Java Back-end Developer
My responsibilities	 Research new technologies and analyst bussinness Responsibilities of serveral modules: Authentication and Security, Netconf gateway, ssh service, Estimate time and report to the leader. Implement the approved solution.
Technologies used	- Java 8, Spring Boot, Spring SecuritMariaDb, Redis, WebSocket, Microservice, IDE: Intellij

Specialty (9/2019 - 2/2020)

Customer	From Vietnam
Description	- An e-commerce application in Vietnam that sells goods made of coffee.
Team size	8
My position	Java Back-end Developer
My responsibilities	 Learn the new technologies and training for team Design systems Estimate time Consult with the customer and decide the business. Implement the approved solution.
Technologies used	- Java EE, MS-SQL, Android, IOS, Wildfly container - Third-party features like Vnpay, Vinaphone Sms - GG play link: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=com.mercafespecialty.ecommerce&hl=vi

Mimerol

(3/2019 - 9/2019)

Customer	From Nicaragua
Description	- An order food online application in Nicaragua base on website https://www.vietnammm.com/
Team size	6
My position	Java Back-end Developer
My responsibilities	 Learn the new technologies and training for team Design systems Estimate time Consult with the customer and decide the business. Implement the approved solution. Write testing cases and unit tests.
	- Spring Boot, MySQL, Angular 6, Android, AWS EC2 - Third-party libraries like Google Map, Firebase Cloud Message,

Technologies used	Twilio, Website: https://mimerol.com/
	- GG play link: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=com.bmbsoft.mimerol

Data Smis

(11/2018 - 2/2019)

Customer	From Japanese
Description	- Work with my team to develop a web application using Seasar and JDBC
Team size	4
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	 Learn the new technologies and training for team Design systems Estimate time Consult with the project manager. Implement the approved solution. Write testing cases and unit tests.
Technologies used	- Java, Oracle, Javascript, HTML, and CSS - Resin , Seasar Framework, S2JDBC

Hamee App (9/2018 - 11/2018)

Customer	From Japanese
Description	- Work with my team to develop a web application using Spring Boot, which allows our clients (online shops in Japan) manage their orders and inventories.
Team size	5
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	 Receive tasks directly from the customer Fix bugs Design systems Estimate time Consult with team leaders Implement the approved solution.
Technologies used	- Java, MYSQL, Javascript, HTML, and CSS - Tomcat container, Spring Boot, JPA, Docker

GMS

(2017 - 2018)

Customer	From Autralia
Description	- This is the web application that helps people quoting, booking domestic or international carrier and generating reports
Team size	8
My position	Developer
	- Analysis and design - Development

My responsibilities	- Review code - Optimize code - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	- Java, MYSQL, Javascript, HTML and CSS - Tomcat container, Spring Framework, Struts2, MyBatis